jobcentral.com 2005-12-16

# JobCentral - Employment Network

JobCentral and NACElink respect the privacy of every individual who visits our web sites or interacts with us in any way. This Privacy Policy states how JobCentral will collect information and use it appropriately. [NACElink’s privacy policy](http://www.nacelink.com/nl_privacy_policy.asp) discloses what information it collects, how the information is used, and how to correct or change it.

Personal Information  
There are several opportunities on our web site for you to provide us with personal information about you and your interests, such as name, mailing address and e-mail address. If you choose to share any personal information with us, we may store it and use it for internal marketing research and other marketing purposes. We will not sell or in any way distribute your personal information to other companies.

Resume Database  
JobCentral provides a resume database for the convenience of job seekers and member companies as well as non-member companies and individuals who are charged a nominal fee to access the resumes. Neither JobCentral nor any other career site on the Internet can assure you that the information on your resume will not be collected and shared with others. JobCentral has a standard ["Terms and Conditions of Service"](http://www.jobcentral.com/tandc.asp) policy which governs the use of information, including resumes, obtained from the JobCentral site. Be aware that such "terms and conditions of use", although valid and enforceable, do not protect your resume from being collected and distributed in a manner you may not desire. Always be aware of [privacy issues](http://www.pamdixon.com/resumedatabaseguide.htm) and possible ["scams"](http://www.worldprivacyforum.org/jobscamtipspayforwarding.html) when submitting your resume online. 

Non-Personal Information  
Sometimes, we may collect non-personal information about you that is anonymous data. The information we receive is for JobCentral’s use only and is not disclosed to any other party except in aggregate form. Examples of this information include the length and time of your visit, the pages you looked at on our site, the type of Internet Browser you have and the site you visited just before coming to ours. We use this information to develop ideas for improving our site and to measure site activity. 

Cookies  
Our web site makes use of 'cookie' files to customize information to your personal tastes. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your Browser, which may store some information on your computer. Then, when you come back to our site, we can tailor information to suit your individual preferences. The goal is to save you time and provide you with a more meaningful visit. Most Internet Browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instruction 

Surveys  
We request your input to evaluate potential features and services for JobCentral. The decision to be involved is completely yours. Also, we might e-mail you a survey, but your involvement is completely voluntary. We do not employ special tools or try to find any e-mail addresses that are not provided to us by you. 

Site Links  
JobCentral may establish relationships with reputable business partners that allow visitors to our site to link directly to sites operated by these partners. We choose our business partners carefully. However, JobCentral is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of third party web sites that may be linked to this site. These links are meant for the user's convenience only and do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement or approval by JobCentral of the content, policies or practices of such sites nor any products or services which may be offered through that site. Once you have left the JobCentral site via such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site. 

The [NACElink](http://www.nacelink.com/) web site is owned and operated by the National Association of Colleges and Employers (NACE). NACE is committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information of the people who use NACElink. Since NACElink collects certain types of information about its users, you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. [NACElink’s privacy policy](http://www.nacelink.com/nl_privacy_policy.asp) discloses what information is collected, how it is used, and how to correct and change it. NACE provides a link to this privacy policy on all pages on NACElink.com that ask for your personal information.

Children  
JobCentral has no intention of collecting any personal information from individuals under 18 years of age. If a child has provided us with personal information without the consent of a parent or guardian, a parent or guardian should contact us at: [info@JobCentral.com](mailto:info@JobCentral.com), if they would like us to delete this information from our files. 

Contact Information  
JobCentral is a wholly owned and operated service of [DirectEmployers Association](http://www.directemployers.org/). If you have questions, comments, or need additional information about JobCentral's privacy policy or practices, please contact us at: [info@JobCentral.com](mailto:info@JobCentral.com). You may also call JobCentral at 1-866-268-6206, or send U.S. mail to: JobCentral, 11 Fortune Park, 4th Floor, 4040 Vincennes Circle, Indianapolis, IN 46268

NACElink is a wholly owned and operated service of the [ National Association of Colleges and Employers (NACE)](http://www.naceweb.org/). If you have questions, comments, or need additional information about NACE or NACElink privacy policies or practices, please contact NACE at: [privacy@nacelink.com](mailto:privacy@nacelink.com). You may also call NACE at 1-800-544-5272, or send U.S. mail to: National Association of Colleges and Employers, 62 Highland Avenue, Bethlehem, PA 18017-9085
